And one year
Professor Cima, when
he was teaching this
class, told the class
that they had to come to the
lottery for the glassblowing
class, and it's a big class.
And so dutifully everyone
came to the lottery,
and we already have about
150 students plus 3091.
And the lottery
was in room 6120,
so we overflowed it by a lot.
So I told Michael, don't
ever do that again, please.
Which is why I do it every year.
But we like 3091 students.
We'll try to give
them preference.
[LAUGHTER]
Trying to work it for you.
He says that.
How many of you have seen
Prince Rupert drops before?
Some people, yeah.
There's a lot of online
stuff about them,
but you get to see
a live one today.
So what's the difference
between a Prince Rupert drop
and tempered glass like
the type [INAUDIBLE]??
Anybody want to take
a guess at that?
They're both under
stress, but the stress
is generated in a different way.